I'm on a journey out to see the world.
While I'm on my own, I've
yet to reach the end.
So won't you come along with me right now?
Surely then we can!
Follow me now as we
journey on from sea to sea.
For that treasure known
by everybody as One Piece.
Even though they laugh and
say it's just a fantasy.
We are going, there's no doubt we go.
Cause we can feel the
rush of energy overcome.
It will lead the way.
Keep pretending that you know what to do.
Books will only get in the way.
No guides for today.
Do not worry soon.
The rain will be gone with the wind.
Keep your chin up, raise the anchor.
Now that's what you'll do.
Give it time and calm.
The storm that you have built within.
Come and have my board at number two.
Once tomorrow's wind picks up.
We set stuff cause we can't.
Thresh it up, stand tall.
And take a look at one of you.
All the journey makes
me want to see somebody.
There are things out there
you just won't believe.
Beyond your wildest dreams.
Don't think for a second.
It's not the truth.
That's the story.
Most will believe.
Not me.
Come and see.
I am on a journey.
Out to see the world.
Don't all on my own.
I've got my group of friends.
Together we've got our way.
That's how it's done.
Says your captain.
Who says it can't be done.
We haven't even tried.
Gotta just believe we'll
make it to the end.
I just wanna do it all right now.
Together surely we can.
Yes, we can.
You can.
Just take this moment in.
We can.
I can.
Just take this feeling in.
Right now.
Oh yes, we can.
I can't find any documents related
to their trafficking deals.
Too convenient.
Obviously, somebody made off with them.
I thought as much.
It's the same story on my end.
All the weapons and explosives that were
left behind disappeared just as quickly.
It was no small amount, either.
The Navy was panicked, too.
Must have been a large organization.
Like the Revolutionary Army?
That seems likely.
Anyway, it's time to go.
Palik.
Quite the nuisance, aren't they?
I couldn't agree more, boss.
Almost as irksome as you. Ha-hoo!
Wow!
Sticking it to him, huh?
Now the question is, where
is Straw Hat going next?
This is a land of tragedy.
One that was beset by dark strings,
pulling its history in woeful directions.
And when the tragedies
piled up too high to count,
what could they do but drown out
their sorrows with the sound of music?
The sound of guitar, of feet
stomping, of hands clapping.
Until at last, the curtain
falls on this long performance.
A tragedy with no name.
As the music goes silent,
the truth rings out clearly.
The king has returned, and the path it
stretches out before them is one of peace.
I would like to propose
a suggestion to everyone.
All right.
I suppose that's the
cue to introduce myself.
I'm Gancho, Chief Donut.
Standing next to me here is my daughter.
My name's Moncherry.
She's so cute!
You want us to make this?
Is that right? Yes, please.
It's a real important job.
The Referee World Summit is this year.
It's coming soon, too.
We'd better get ready.
Can't be left behind, you know?
Father, good news.
Rebecca said she'll be stopping by early
this afternoon to cook some lunch for us.
Is that so? And Course?
Actually, he's coming too.
Well, that's wonderful.
Seems we'll have the whole
family together again.
It's been a while.
In the future,
those who come to visit
this kingdom will be
met with a surprise like
none other in the world.
Can I get a hat?
Would you look who it is?
Rebecca and Monterey.
Alongside the humans of the city, Tiny
Tomtata can be found living and thriving.
Hey, shouldn't we focus on
building houses first? No way!
This is our first priority.
Such an adorable sight may turn
into a tourist attraction itself.
This is a kingdom of love,
passion, and fairies.
I guess the statues are
important too. That's right!
Dress Rosa.
Once we finish transporting the
prisoner, I'll be heading on a journey.
A journey?
I can't set foot inside
any Navy base. Remember?
Not unless I turn in Straw Hat and Law.
You're so stubborn.
All you have to do is apologize and
then Sakazuki can save face easily.
I don't want to.
And why not?
Because I want to save face too.
Right, fine. Well...
Oh, Fujitora.
I'm telling you, Tsuru,
that man's an idiot.
He had one last chance
to do the right thing.
To side with me and eliminate all of those
brats before they caused any more trouble.
Now look at where we are.
I was holding the reins, you know.
The reins on all the monsters
that threaten this world.
Taking me down was a terrible mistake.
Just you wait.
You'll regret this decision soon enough.
Do you really believe the crap
that comes out of your mouth?
Don't be so delusional.
Everything would have worked out if
only we'd helped you, is that it?
Well, we didn't, so you can deal with it.
It's over and you lost.
Wow, you really aren't going
to give an inch, are you?
It takes a thief to know one.
So what do you think will happen
to the world of pirates now?
Let me answer that question
with one of my own.
What do you think happens
to monsters once they've
lost their source of food
and are off their leashes?
Is there anyone who rules these
seas who can reign them in?
Who possesses the most power, the
most influence in these waters?
One of the four emperors, perhaps?
Or the seven warlords
who struck a clever deal?
Maybe the brats from the
worst generation running wild?
Not quite.
After all, we can't ignore the Navy,
swinging around their hammer of justice,
or the formidable fighters
of the Revolutionary Army.
who struggle fearlessly
for the common man.
Or will those with the will of D
walk in the shadows of history?
When and where will they
decide to show themselves?
Who's gonna side with who?
Who will betray who?
I have a message for you
to give the celestial.
Dragons in Marie Joie tell them they
will be dragged from their gilded halls.
It's been 25 years since gold Roger
conquered the Grand Line and no one's
done it since his rival White Beard
stood before the throne but met his end,
having never sat upon it.
So what happens now?
You think there are more pirates
running wild out there than ever before,
but there's just one empty seat.
You get it now.
All those pirates are about to
have a struggle for supremacy.
The mask is burning!
Put it out!
Are we headed to Impel Down?
In that case, I have a small request.
I need you to bring me
a newspaper every day.
Then at least I'll never be bored.
Looks like four Navy ships, but it's wild.
They've got so many heavy hitters,
even though this is just a transfer.
That's enough strength
to crush a whole country.
They're not taking
chances with Doflamingo.
Ah, bad news, Master Jack.
Looks like we can't get Joker.
Should we turn around? What?
Don't tell me what I can't
do, you piece of crap!
Who the hell do you think I am?
I don't like this at all.
It's like your ship has more
Luffy on it than ours does.
I'm so flattered that it stinks so well.
Are you listening?
There's something on this ship
more exciting than anything else.
And this fever cod here
is showing us the way.
It's the real Mr. Luffy.
It's truly an honor to
have you here, Mr. Luffy.
I never imagined my wildest
dreams would come true.
He's shining so brightly I can't even see.
It's a real struggle, I gotta tell you.
They're all families, huh?
Funny how everything worked
out with the Vivre card.
I guess we have Sabo to thank for that.
All right, this is a fever card of Luffy.
I had one made up, huh?
When did that happen?
I'll be taking a piece
as well, hell yeah! Mrs.
Sabo is the man!
He's the perfect big brother.
Strong and nice—listen, Luffy!
I'm not gonna be your
follower like the rest.
But
I'll take a piece just in case.
Okay, fine by me; should
be enough for everyone.
Looks
like it's farewell for now.
We'll meet again soon, boss!
No doubt in my mind.
Until next time—Straw Hat!
See you guys. Good luck.
Man, that
was one heck of a party, huh?
Those guys really grew on me, Bartholomew!
Stop wasting time!
wasting time
Huh?
I don't take quarters from you.
We should hurry.
Of course! On it, Mr. Zoro!
You heard the man! Straight for Zo!
Full speed ahead!
Yes, sir!
I wonder if the rest of the crew
made it safely to the island.
Nami was with them, so I know
they didn't lose their way.
But if Big Mom catches them,
that could be bad news.
It worries me.
Hey, Luffy.
I'm reading the paper, and it looks
like our bounties just went up.
Huh?
I want to see it! Oh, yeah?
I thought you already knew!
Incidentally, I have
your posters in my room.
Come this way! Hooray!
You were ready for this, huh?
I threw yours away, but your
bounty's up to 500 million. Yeah?
Thanks, I guess.
I don't really care about that crap.
Now, gaze upon your own glory!
You framed them?
Yeah, along with the
autographs you gave me.
Shall we begin?
First of all, Straw Hat
Luffy, 500 million berries.
Yeah, I'm getting up there.
Next up is Pirate Hunter
Zoro, 320 million berries.
Nice.
Can we celebrate with a drink?
demon child nico robin
130 million berries.
Oh my, it's gone up!
cyborg Franky 94 million berries.
So close to a hundred!
Also, that's general Franky, not me.
Go on! Who's up?
200 million. Ha!
They actually got my
face and name this time!
They're coming for me!
Put that bounty.
What's with that awful picture, though?
Hey!
What the hell, bro?
Why is your bounty so
high and mine so low? Ah!
Even my own crewmates are coming for me!
I just want to be 100 million, too.
You're all more than me.
You don't know that?
Let's look at the rest of them first.
Blackfoot Sanji, 177 million berries.
Hey, it's not that weird
drawing anymore. He'll be happy.
Tch, this one sucks.
Now I can't laugh at him anymore.
Cat Boigler Nami, 66 million berries.
She posed for her picture again?
When did that happen?
Cotton Candy Lover Chopper, 100.
Ooh, I don't want to be the
one to break the news to him.
So, oh, King Brook.
83 million berries.
That's just one of his show posters.
What the hell? Wow!
Some of yous, like Mr.
Luffy, made a pretty
big splash in Dressrosa,
so your bounties went up a whole bunch.
But everyone else across the
board went up by 50 million.
That goes for all the
folks on my crew, too.
But, uh...
I noticed something weird
about Mr. Sanji's poster.
Even though he didn't see much
action, his bounty went way up.
Also, look at the text.
Huh?
Only alive?
I'm sure it's nothing.
It's hail!
Careful, guys. They're huge.
It smashed the whole rank
through the deck! Mr.
Lupi, get back!
And everyone else, too!
I'm not gonna hide!
We're gonna help you!
So, but you're returning.
Where's your navigator?
What do they advise?
Yeah, about that.
The thing is, we're land
pirates, so they got one?
Ah!
This is the new world, though!
It's me, Gambia!
Sup, Granny?
Hey, you got a minute to tell
me what you know about Hale?
See, when we're in trouble, his grandma
always knows what to do and bails us out.
Great.
You do have someone competent to help.
I got a hot tip!
Know that pile of chewing gum?
The one stuck to the ship's deck?
Oh, yeah!
No one could get it off!
She said to grab some hail, wrap it in
a hanky, and freeze the gum with it!
Okay! Whoa!
Well, I'll be fast!
It came right up!
That's what she said!
But we're in danger! Come on!
See?
It didn't help!
Yo, Granny says sugar that lump!
Enough of her full wisdom!
Oh, crap!
The ship's going down!
Help us, Nami!
We just had to choose this one! Typical.
Guess it's up to us to fix this. Damn it.
If only I had to Sunny's equipment.
How fun.
Hey, what's wrong? Barrier.
Well, it's just Granny said,
if you get in nature's way,
then you'll pay the price.
Live on land, you damn
chicken. Come on. For real?
You see this?
We're so blessed.
They don't fear no forces in nature.
They're unshakable.
Our appreciation rains down on hail.
How the hell are you all still alive?
I'm so happy.
Do something, idiots.
The AO pirates, formerly Whitebeard's
men, have been wiped out.
Was it him again?
Yes, the warlord, Edward Weevil.
More pirates who worked
under Whitebeard, huh?
Remind me, how many captains
has he put down in all?
Sixteen now, sir.
Hmm.
First they have some sort of disagreement,
then he takes them out along
with whatever town they're in.
As usual, he leaves a big mess.
In addition to the collateral damage,
the death tolls at about six hundred.
He may be a warlord, but we can't
exactly turn a blind eye here.
Yes, it's quite the quandary.
Not just that, but Weevil also claims to
be the biological son of Edward Newgate,
though not too many people are buying it.
Hmm.
Well, whether or not it's the
truth is of no consequence to us.
Lineage aside, he does
have one valuable trait.
Edward Weevil is a
tremendously powerful pirate.
In fact, he's just like
Whitebeard was as a young man,
in terms of his physical strength at least
though that's all they have in common
a week after departing dress rosa it's
too foggy i can't see a damn thing
how are all of you seasick and you
call yourselves a pirate crew Gum-Gum
my granny always told me chewing gum
soothes the tummy are you kidding
me is that why the whole ship is
covered in it these guys are great
hey boss i think i see something
at two o 'clock be more specific man
it's hard to make out it could be a
mountain or a monster if you can't tell
then either you need an eye exam or
we're in big trouble it's really slow
but i'm pretty sure it's on the move
maybe you just drunk a moving mountain
let's go see are you crazy here's a
thought how about we get out of this foggy
maze asap if we get something we'll be
capsized hang on god oh you don't have
to call me god that's so nice must be
the 200 million huh with a bounty like
that i'm sure the navy's hot on your
trail now let's see looks like the veaver
card is pointing that way whoa you're
right must mean your friends are there
dear do you need some gum too you
look ill I've been trying not to
think about that they say Zoe is
naturally resistant to invaders because
of the fog and the strong current
we've got a headwind to taking the
sails let's row this baby forward
come on you can do better than that
wait a minute are you sure
this is oh oh Danny right
then we should leave turn
the sticky ship around
we're here believe it
or not uh
traffic
i don't
think that's an island
looks more like an animal
yeah the land of zo rests on the
back of a giant elephant What?
How the heck does that work?
As the beast moves around,
those coordinates change.
So it's called a phantom island.
That's why you can't use
a log post to get to it.
It's my first time here as well.
Since it's showing it's back to us,
that might mean Blackfoot's group
got here long before we did.
So all this time, it's been
steadily moving away from us?
Yeah.
Let's get ready to disembark.
Can you guys spare us some of your food?
Not for you, freeloader.
It isn't for me.
It's for Straw Hat.
Sure, take all you want.
Help yourself.
So this is Zo.
Truly, there are countless wonders
to be found outside our country.
I hope Momonosuke is safe.
Wait, I've heard that the
inhabitants of Zo are hostile.
Yeah, so they say.
They're called the Minks
for a thousand years.
All humans have been banned here, huh?
So this place has been
around for that long.
Hold on, that means the elephant's
like a thousand years old.
Oh, this is too good to be true!
Would you chill out?
Beautiful.
It's really here.
The ship that carries
Straw Hats everywhere.
So they can spread awesomeness
all over the world.
The thousand sunni as I live and breathe.
What did I do to deserve such an honor?
Please
We're not working!
That's creepy.
Oh, good.
So they did make it to Zoe before we did.
Yeah, and it looks like they got
away from Big Mom safely, too.
I don't see any major damage.
Hey, Sanji!
Nami!
Chopper! Brook!
Momo!
And, uh, that guy with the gas!
Hurry, Strawheads!
You gotta cross over!
Where are they?
Oh, yeah, no need to wait
for an invitation from me!
Do you see anyone?
I'm pretty sure they left. It's fine.
Maybe they got here early.
Well, be careful out there.
You're coming too, moron.
I wish I could tag along.
Just so I could bask in the
warmth of their greatness.
for a little bit longer.
But I'm sure a regular
guy like me would only
get in the way of their godlike adventure.
That's okay.
Our happiness providence
already backs out anyway.
You will never be cool enough
to join the Straw Hat Pirates,
but I swear the next time we see you guys,
we'll have abilities that'll make
us worthy of being called servants.
of the Straw Hats at least.
Oh, and if we help you again, can we
please have a little something in return?
The other four autographs
from the rest of the crew.
I missed out on meeting them.
I know it's kind of a big ask, but we'd
be so proud if we owed the whole set.
A worm?
Or a snake?
It's got legs. I say listen.
They're ignoring me.
It's like I'm not even here.
They're so focused on the job in here.
Oh, no!
There.
Some of my finest work, I'd say.
What is it, though?
A snake, I told you. What? A snake?
Are you certain?
Ah.
Up here, rising dragon. Dragon? Yeah.
Whoa.
All right.
This is going to be so cool.
No way!
Come on, dragons aren't
supposed to be wimpy!
Really now?
An eye for an eye, my friend.
So cute.
Make haste, everyone!
Climb upon it so that we might be
carried upward so it can't fly!
Awesome!
Let's go!
You can do it, Big Eye!
How much further do we have to go?
I can't even see the top.
You sure you got the right giant elephant?
Everything's fine.
The Viva card's still pointing up.
If you say so.
All right, Dragon, do your stuff!
Hey, Romeo!
Thanks for bringing us here!
You and your crew were a big help!
He sank, but I think he said...
He almost called me by my name!
I'm so happy for you, boss!
Don't mention it, Mr.
Luffy The pleasure was all ours Please
be careful on your new adventure, okay?
Same to you, booty.
See you later.
This is the happiest day of my life.
Having said their farewells.
The crew continued their climb to the
top of the phantom island of Zola.
Commander, rebel forces are
winning all across the world.
Clearly, the defeat of the Don Quixote
family had a significant impact.
With all these nations involved in
weapon trafficking, I'm not surprised.
This is good news.
But, tell the men not to get
too comfortable. Yes, sir.
The world government won't have it.
And Cypher-Pol's been
reinforced in recent years.
That's why we need to stay on our guard.
Right.
Dragon, sir.
The weapons we brought from Dressrosa,
they found a special metal inside them.
What'd you mean?
It's called drunken iron ore.
Only a few countries can
mine it, so it's really rare.
Which means we might be able to find
out where the weapons were first made.
That's excellent news, then. Indeed.
And you brought our lost
comrades back as well.
You've done some impressive
work. Who, me? Not at all.
Sabo and Luffy helped out a lot.
Any news about Robin?
I heard she was caught in Sabo Odi,
but it turned out that wasn't true.
She's fine.
In fact, she seems really full of life.
Just like...
Hold on, don't you want
to know about Luffy?
I've already heard enough oh I guess
Sabo gave you the full report huh anyway
Koala yes we need to ask for help from
them them sir go summon the leaders
of the revolutionary army from all
over the world right oh geez it's gonna
get intense with all of them together
though
yes
this is
lafitte it's purchase
you hear me purchase yes of course we
went to dress rosa to pick you up but you
weren't there yeah sorry I was out cold
for a while there so
I couldn't contact you
well how do you like that bastard was
alive so what have you been up to all of
this time where are you now
I'm
stowed
away I snuck down into the bottom of a
ship.
Tell Captain Teach something for me.
If we invade this place, we'll be up
to our eyeballs and free weapons easy.
I've told you countless times.
It's Commodore Teach.
And make sure to send Doc Q, would you?
I'm at death's doorstep over here.
Burgess, enough of this. Tell us where
you are.
I don't know what the place is called,
but it's some uncharted island.
Just follow my Make it
quick dragons here too,
and so is that pain in the ass named Sabo?
That's right!
I found it.
This is where the Revolutionary
Army's headquarters are.
Why does everybody have to be
such big, stupid, dumb jerks?
They won't stop telling those
mean lies and making me mad.
The only sons that Whitebeard ever had
were the Whitebeard Pirate, they all say.
Mommy! Mommy!
They're wrong, because
Whitebeard is my daddy, right?
My beard's white, too.
Of course my treasure!
Those Whitebeard Pirates
were never a real family.
Whitebeard was the strongest
pirate in the world,
and you're the only
biological son he ever had.
We're his family.
Because I was his one true lover.
So hold your head high, sweet son of mine!
They're giving me a boo-boo.
Look at this. Huh?
A mirror?
No, dear.
It's a picture of Whitebeard. Really?
But it looks just like me, though.
That's exactly the point I'm
trying to make you don't.
You two couldn't look more alike.
Okay.
Sorry, I'm stupid, Mommy.
I know.
I forgive you.
After all, you're my precious boy.
Oh, shucks.
All right, let's move it.
Now then, can you tell
Mommy what your job is?
Let's see.
I forgot.
First, you have to track down who's
left of the Whitebeard Pirates,
like Marco the Phoenix, for instance?
and then you take what's yours.
Edward Newgate must have left
behind a substantial fortune,
and as his only descendant, the
entirety of said fortune belongs to you.
Oh, right, right. Ooh!
Hey!
Wait, Mommy.
Money's OK, but what I
really want is revenge.
Blackbeard's going to
pay for killing my daddy.
I'll never forgive that big bully.
I'm going to beat him up
till he's caught at 10.
Foolish boy, where's the
sense in getting even?
You can't pay the bills
with revenge, you know.
What we need is money.
Go and claim what belongs to you.
Yes, Mommy, I will.
What does the newspaper say?
Doflamingo just got taken out.
It's that brat again, Carp's grandson.
They say Marco and the others protected
him during the Battle of Marineford.
Maybe he knows where to find Marco.
Let's go pummel him.
We're going to have a problem.
Chairman Buggy! What is it?
The snails are ringing off the
hook with new job requests.
That's wonderful.
Now that nobody can get weapons
from Doflamingo anymore,
everyone's looking to
hire pirate mercenaries.
to take care of all
their fighting for them.
We've taken over the military market.
That's just what I like to hear.
Listen up, everybody.
As soon as you're finished eating,
I want you to get out there and
pillage to your heart's content.
After all, it's legitimate now.
If it's done in my name, that makes it the
legal business of a warlord of the sea.
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Oh, yeah, Chairman Buggy.
I forgot to tell you, we got a call
from our Scales mercenary, Hirudin.
He says he wants to quit. He what?
Well, it's not a huge loss
if it's only one giant.
We still got four others, don't we?
It's all of them. What?
But that's the most
lucrative group we've got!
Why would they quit just when
we're starting to get busy?
I don't think you want to know. Try me!
Spit it out!
You can't see to the top.
I wonder how Sanji and
them made it up that high.
Do you think maybe they didn't?
Wolf and the others are
scaling the left leg of the
gargantuan beast by riding on the
back of another strange thing.
We're so high! I'm terrified!
And my arms are giving out!
I hate this!
Don't say that, Usopp!
He's doing the best he can!
Kine-man, Kanjuro, why did the two of
you want to go to Zo in the first place?
Right, we haven't said.
We're in your debt, so the least
we can do is tell you the truth.
But it's a complicated matter.
Indeed, though Zo has been our destination
ever since we first departed, Wano.
For now, I can tell you this.
Firstly, we are concerned
about Momonosuke's well-being.
We also hope to be reunited
with our friend Raizo,
a ninja who was separated from us at sea.
A ninja?
A real ninja? Oh, my.
That's so cool.
Let's find this guy.
Look up there, Luffy.
Something's falling toward us.
Huh?
That came out of nowhere.